trymyapps.com 2016-06-15

# Privacy Policy about TryMyApps.com

Ignition Mobile Corporation recognizes the privacy concerns of visitors to our site on the Internet (www.trymyapps.com). Specifically, Ignition Mobile recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about the visitors our website. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, or email address, is automatically collected when you visit our site. Ignition Mobile may collect certain non-personal information, which is used only to optimize Ignition Mobile Web pages for your computer or mobile phone (e.g., the identity of your Internet browser, the type of operating system you use, and the domain name of your Internet service provider). This non-personal information may also be used by Ignition Mobile to determine the total number of visitors to our website. Personally identifiable information about visitors to Ignition Mobile site is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. In those instances when Ignition Mobile does collect such information, the following applies: How We Use Data Collected on This Site Except as described in this Privacy Policy, personally identifiable information that is submitted knowingly and voluntarily by visitors to the Ignition Mobile site is retained by Ignition Mobile and is not sold or otherwise transferred to an outside company, unless otherwise stated at the time of collection. 

| 

Ignition Mobile will notify you when it is collecting personally identifiable information about you, as well as the use or uses Ignition Mobile intends to make of such information. Information is used in aggregate. No personally identifiable information is reported or used. 

| 

By using this site, you agree to the Privacy Policy of Ignition Mobile. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use this site. Ignition Mobile reviews its Privacy Policy periodically and reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Policy at anytime. This page should be reviewed from time to time so that you are updated on any changes.
